<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

 <Altar_Grand_nuclear.label>Megaton</Altar_Grand_nuclear.label>
<Altar_Grand_nuclear.description>Before you lies an unexploded atomic bomb, a reminder of the conflict that destroyed civilization. Lo! He comes with the clouds! And every eye shall be blinded by his glory! Every ear shall be deaf to the thunder of his voice! Let the men, women, and children of Earth come forth to gather and behold the power of the Atom! Let those who dwell here in his blessed land heed the words of the Prophet of the Atom! Come and drink of the waters of Radiance, for this ancient weapon of war is our salvation, the very symbol of the glory of the Atom! Let it serve as a reminder of the Separation that took place in the past, and of the splendor of the promise of our separation in the times to come! Give your bodies to the Atom, my friends. Surrender to its power, feel its Radiance and be Separated. There will be no tears, no sorrow, no suffering, for in Separation we will see our release from the pain and burdens of this world. Yes, your suffering will be no more; it will be washed away in the Radiance of the Atom, burned from you in the fire of its brilliance. Each of us will give birth to a billion stars, formed from the mass of our wretched and filthy bodies. Each of us will be the mother and father of a trillion civilizations. Each of us will know peace, know the end of pain and know the Atom in its glory. I call upon you, my friends, come and drink with me and pray... Glorious Atom, I give you these weak bones. I present to your will this frail body. I beg you to use me as your vessel, to direct me to your radiance, to divide each particle and give relief to this rotten flesh. Cast off the frail form of this ephemeral body into a new life in the forge of your Radiance. Atom, come - grant your presence to your unworthy servant. We remain faithful, until the Day of Separation - until the dawn of your return to His humble world.</Altar_Grand_nuclear.description>


</LanguageData>